{
  "posts": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "title": "json-server",
      "author": "typicode"
    }
  ],
  "comments": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "body": "some comment",
      "postId": 1
    }
  ],
  "profile": {
    "name": "typicode"
  },
  "quiz": [
    {
      "question": "Which Pokemon is known for carrying a leek?",
      "a": "Farfetch'd",
      "b": "Pikachu",
      "c": "Squirtle",
      "d": "Oddish",
      "answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these pokemon is not an electric type??",
      "a": "Jolteon",
      "b": "Pikachu",
      "c": "Porygon",
      "d": "Voltorb",
      "answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these pokemon is a starter Pokemon in the Kanto Region?",
      "a": "Ghastly",
      "b": "Torchic",
      "c": "Togepi",
      "d": "Squirtle",
      "answer": "d"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many pokemon were available in Generation 1?",
      "a": "100",
      "b": "138",
      "c": "151",
      "d": "150",
      "answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many gym badges can a pokemon trainer obtain in the Kanto Region?",
      "a": "8",
      "b": "10",
      "c": "5",
      "d": "16",
      "answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Pokemon evolves from Eevee?",
      "a": "Lapras",
      "b": "Espeon",
      "c": "Houndoom",
      "d": "Mewtwo",
      "answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which evolution stone allows Vulpix to evolve?",
      "a": "Dusk Stone",
      "b": "Water Stone",
      "c": "Fire Stone",
      "d": "Leaf Stone",
      "answer": "c"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the newest pokemon region",
      "a": "Kanto",
      "b": "Galar",
      "c": "Hoenn",
      "d": "Johto",
      "answer": "b"
    },
    {
      "question": "Of which type are there the least pokemon?",
      "a": "Water",
      "b": "Normal",
      "c": "Dragon",
      "d": "Ghost",
      "answer": "d"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these pokemon is viewed as the mascot of the Pokemon Company?",
      "a": "Eevee",
      "b": "Pikachu",
      "c": "Vulpix",
      "d": "Clefairy",
      "answer": "b"
    }
  ]
}